<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content" xmlns:newsmail="//">
  <channel>
    <title>AUDI 349</title>
    <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://qa1.kansascity.com/feeds/fulltext/newsletter/AUDI_349" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link>
    <description></description>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2020 The Kansas City Star</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 11:04:54 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <newsmail:editor_note>false</newsmail:editor_note>
    <item>
      <title>EE.UU: Muertes por coronavirus alcanzan niveles récord</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739564.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739564.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>LISA MARIE PANE y RACHEL LA CORTE</dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:15:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/hq1bpm/picture18739558/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/CORONAVIRUS-EEUU_03683.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>ARCHIVO - En esta foto del 7 de diciembre del 2020, enfermeros de cuidados intensivos y terapeutas respiratorios tratan a un paciente con COVID-19 en el Hospital North Memorial Health en Robbinsdale, Minnesota. (Aaron Lavinsky/Star Tribune via AP)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Aaron Lavinsky</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/hq1bpm/picture18739558/alternates/FREE_320/CORONAVIRUS-EEUU_03683.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <category>AMN</category>
      <category>GEN CORONAVIRUS</category>
      <category>EEUU</category>
      <description>Las muertes por COVID-19 en Estados Unidos aumentan a un promedio superior a las 2.200 diarias , igualando el pico alcanzado en abril, y los casos por día han eclipsado el promedio de 200.000 por primera vez, en una crisis que casi seguramente empeorará debido a los viajes y reuniones familiares de la temporada navideña.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Las muertes por COVID-19 en Estados Unidos han aumentado hasta superar las 2.200 diarias en promedio, igualando el pico alcanzado en abril, y los casos por día han eclipsado el promedio de 200.000 por primera vez, en una crisis que casi seguramente empeorará debido a los viajes y reuniones familiares de la temporada navideña.</p>
<p>Prácticamente todos los estados reportan aumentos de casos, en momentos en que la vacuna parece estar a días de recibir la luz verde en Estados Unido.</p>
<p>“Lo que hagamos ahora literalmente será un asunto de vida o muerte para muchos de nuestros ciudadanos”, dijo el gobernador de Washington Jay Inslee el martes al extender las restricciones a negocios y reuniones sociales, incluyendo una prohibición del servicio bajo techo en restaurantes y bares.</p>
<p>Aunque la inminente llegada de la vacuna es motivo de esperanza, dijo, “por el momento tenemos que enfrentar la realidad, y la realidad es que estamos en una situación muy funesta con la pandemia”.</p>
<p>El virus ha causado más de 285.000 muertes y 15 millones de casos confirmados en Estados Unidos.</p>
<p>Muchos estadounidenses hicieron caso omiso a las advertencias de no viajar para el feriado de Acción de Gracias y han ignorado otras medidas de precaución, ya sea por necedad, ignorancia o autocomplacencia. El sábado por la noche, la policía en el norte de California arrestó a casi 160 personas, muchas de ellas sin mascarillas, en una fiesta ilegal en una casa en Palmdale que fue realizada sin conocimiento del dueño.</p>
<p>La doctora Deborah Birx, coordinadora del grupo de trabajo de la Casa Blanca contra la pandemia, expresó lo que pareció una ligera crítica a la forma en que el presidente Donald Trump y otros miembros del gobierno han restado importancia a la enfermedad y socavado a los científicos.</p>
<p>“Los mensajes tienen que ser congruentes”, dijo Birx el martes en una conferencia de ejecutivos empresariales auspiciada por el Wall Street Journal. “Pienso que tenemos que ser mucho más coherentes al responder a los mitos — que el COVID-19 no existe, o que las cifras de muertos son inventadas o que las hospitalizaciones son por otras razones, que las mascarillas hacen daño”.</p>
<p> Se prevé que el jueves, el panel asesor de la Administración de Alimentos y Medicamentos apruebe el uso de emergencia de la vacuna de Pfizer y las inyecciones pudieran empezar casi inmediatamente, lo que convertiría a Estados Unidos el primer país en Occidente en iniciar las vacunaciones masivas.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:lead-type>picture</newsmail:lead-type>
      <newsmail:lead-image>https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/hq1bpm/picture18739558/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/CORONAVIRUS-EEUU_03683.jpg</newsmail:lead-image>
      <newsmail:home-section>AUDI 349</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerPoint: On 3-game run, Washington’s Rivera eyes humility</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/sports/article18739555.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/sports/article18739555.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>HOWARD FENDRICH</dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:13:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/4k8v3h/picture18739540/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Washington_Steelers_Football_56518.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Washington Football Team defensive end Chase Young (99) celebrates after a win over the Pittsburgh Steelers in an NFL football game in Pittsburgh, Monday, Dec. 7, 2020. (AP Photo/Barry Reeger)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Barry Reeger</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/4k8v3h/picture18739540/alternates/FREE_320/Washington_Steelers_Football_56518.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/8eg0hd/picture18737482/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Washington_Steelers_Football_19636.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Washington Football Team quarterback Alex Smith (11) throws a 15-yard touchdown pass to Logan Thomas during the second half of an NFL football game against the Pittsburgh Steelers, Monday, Dec. 7, 2020, in Pittsburgh. (AP Photo/Keith Srakocic)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Keith Srakocic</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/8eg0hd/picture18737482/alternates/FREE_320/Washington_Steelers_Football_19636.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/i9red3/picture18739543/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Washington_Steelers_Football_06335.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Washington Football Team tight end Logan Thomas (82) hauls in a 15-yard touchdown pass from quarterback Alex Smith during the second half of an NFL football game against the Pittsburgh Steelers, Monday, Dec. 7, 2020, in Pittsburgh. (AP Photo/Keith Srakocic)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Keith Srakocic</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/i9red3/picture18739543/alternates/FREE_320/Washington_Steelers_Football_06335.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/t9aybi/picture18739546/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Washington_Steelers_Football_88662.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Washington Football Team head coach Ron Rivera, center, walks on the sideline during the first half of an NFL football game against the Pittsburgh Steelers in Pittsburgh, Monday, Dec. 7, 2020. (AP Photo/Barry Reeger)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Barry Reeger</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/t9aybi/picture18739546/alternates/FREE_320/Washington_Steelers_Football_88662.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <category>Washington Analysis</category>
      <description>Coach Ron Rivera wants to make sure his suddenly surging Washington team gets a good dose of humility coming off its biggest win of the season.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Coach Ron Rivera came prepared with a slide presentation to show his players Tuesday, a day after Washington stopped Pittsburgh’s unbeaten run and remained in the thick of the playoff pursuit in the worse-than-mediocre NFC East.</p>
<p>“We’ll have a little lesson today about humility. I’ve got it all set on the PowerPoint,” Rivera said in a video conference with reporters. “Just because we won this game doesn’t mean we’re going to show up somewhere else and win automatically. We’ve got to earn it. That will be one thing that we will talk about.”</p>
<p>Humility? That he’s throwing around that word now shows what a sudden turnaround it’s been for a club that went 3-13 under Jay Gruden last season and opened its first season under Rivera with a 1-5 record.</p>
<p>At 5-7 heading into next weekend’s game against San Francisco — a contest being played in Arizona because the 49ers had to abandon their home stadium because of the coronavirus pandemic — it’s not as if Washington is a juggernaut. But maybe it can be allowed to feel good about itself while essentially standing even with the New York Giants (also 5-7 but at an advantage because of a 2-0 head-to-head mark) in the division.</p>
<p>Three consecutive victories for Alex Smith and the rest of the group will do that sort of thing, especially when the most recent was by a 23-17 score over the Steelers, who went into Monday’s game 11-0.</p>
<p>Rivera noted that it was exactly a year ago Monday — Dec. 7, 2019 — that he and Washington owner Dan Snyder first spoke about the team, five days after the coach was fired by the Carolina Panthers.</p>
<p>“The serendipity of it all was an amazing thing,” Rivera said. “I thought about that during the day, and then after the game, I thought about it.” </p>
<p>WHAT’S WORKING</p>
<p>A defense anchored by a front filled with first-round draft picks such as Chase Young, Montez Sweat and Jonathan Allen really shut down Ben Roethlisberger and Co. down the stretch, limiting the Steelers to merely a field goal after halftime. Washington limited Pittsburgh to 21 yards on the ground overall and harassed Big Ben plenty, including three tipped passes by Sweat, the last of which was picked off by Jon Bostic. Sweat said Roethlisberger chatted with him after one play. “He was a little frustrated. I could tell by his demeanor,” Sweat said. “We were getting under his skin.”</p>
<p>WHAT NEEDS HELP</p>
<p>Washington’s special teams had some issues, including a pair of penalties in the first quarter — blocking in the back by James Smith-Williams and a hold by Khaleke Hudson — and, most egregiously, a failure by Jeremy Sprinkle to recover a fumbled punt return that was his for the grabbing.</p>
<p>STOCK UP</p>
<p>Logan Thomas played quarterback in college, and when he first arrived in the NFL, but eventually switched to tight end and is really blossoming now. He had career bests of nine catches and 98 yards against the Steelers, along with a 15-yard TD connection with Smith, and even jumped in to grab a fourth-quarter fumble by teammate J.D. McKissic, taking the ball away from Pittsburgh’s T.J. Watt. “Logan just continues to grow,” Rivera said.</p>
<p>STOCK DOWN</p>
<p>There was a bad drop by receiver Steven Sims early in Monday’s game, and a 50-yard TD pass from Roethlisberger to James Washington that made it 14-0, but given how the night wound up going, what’s there really for Rivera to complain about? </p>
<p>INJURED</p>
<p>Leading rusher Antonio Gibson limped off the field after his second carry against Pittsburgh and was treated for a left toe injury. The rookie’s status remained a mystery to those outside the team Tuesday, because when Rivera was asked about Gibson, this was the reply: “I don’t talk to the trainers until I get done with this (video conference). It’s just something I try to do — that way I can’t answer your questions and give you the right answer. It’s a way of me avoiding it. Really, that’s it. ... The less our opponent knows, the better.” </p>
<p>KEY NUMBER</p>
<p>2 — The average number of second-half points Washington has allowed opponents during its current winning streak.</p>
<p>NEXT STEPS</p>
<p>Some familiar faces for both teams when head coach Kyle Shanahan, who was Washington’s offensive coordinator from 2010-13, and the 49ers (5-7) play against Smith, who was drafted No. 1 overall by San Francisco in 2005, and Washington in a matchup that could affect the NFC playoff race.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:lead-type>picture</newsmail:lead-type>
      <newsmail:lead-image>https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/4k8v3h/picture18739540/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Washington_Steelers_Football_56518.jpg</newsmail:lead-image>
      <newsmail:home-section>Sports</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Woman arrested at Phoenix airport with a knife hidden in bra</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739573.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739573.html</guid>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:20:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Airport Arrest</category>
      <category>Woman With Knife</category>
      <description>The FBI says a woman was arrested at Phoenix Sky Harbor Airport after allegedly trying to pass through security and board a flight to San Francisco recently with a folding knife concealed in her bra.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A woman was arrested at Phoenix Sky Harbor Airport after allegedly trying to pass through security and board a flight to San Francisco recently with a folding knife concealed in her bra., authorities said Tuesday.</p>
<p>FBI officials in Phoenix said 36-year-old Erine Aisha Robertson was charged with the federal crime of attempting to carry a weapon on an aircraft.</p>
<p>They said the incident occurred on Nov. 28.</p>
<p>Court documents show an alarm went off as Robertson passed through the sensor at the Transportation Security Administration checkpoint. </p>
<p>Authorities said Robertson was taken to a private screening room where she reached into her bra and pulled out a small pocket knife.</p>
<p>Robertson’s hometown wasn’t immediately available and it was unclear Tuesday if Robertson has a lawyer who can speak on her behalf about the case.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:home-section>AUDI 349</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NW Indiana teen gets 179 years in prison for 2 murders</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739570.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739570.html</guid>
      <dc:creator></dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 21:19:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <category>Teens Slain</category>
      <category>Conviction</category>
      <description>A northwest Indiana man convicted of fatally shooting two teenagers during a drug-related robbery has been sentenced to 179 years in prison.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A northwest Indiana man convicted of fatally shooting two teenagers during a drug-related robbery was sentenced Tuesday to 179 years in prison.</p>
<p>A Porter County jury found Connor Kerner, 19, guilty in October of charges including two counts each of murder and murder in perpetration of a robbery.</p>
<p>The Valparaiso man had allegedly confessed to a then-girlfriend that he had killed 18-year-old Thomas Grill of Cedar Lake and 19-year-old Molley Lanham of St. John in February 2019 in the attached garage of his maternal grandparents’ Hebron-area home.</p>
<p>Prosecutors said the target in the robbery that led to the killings was $20,000 to $50,000 worth of THC cartridges.</p>
<p>Kerner showed no obvious reaction to the sentence but said he intends to appeal, The (Northwest Indiana) Times  reported.</p>
<p>Patricia Grill, mother of Thomas Grill, looked down at Kerner and accused him of attempting to erase her son and Lanham.</p>
<p>“You erased your life, Connor,” she said. </p>
<p>Stacy Spejewski, mother of Lanham, said she is still numb nearly two years after her daughter’s killing. “I am now the mother of a murdered child,” she said.</p>
<p>Kerner declined to comment before sentencing, but said he intends to appeal.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:home-section>AUDI 349</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSG, Basaksehir teams walk off after alleged racial slur</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/sports/article18739507.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/sports/article18739507.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>JEROME PUGMIRE</dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:51:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/a5veku/picture18739501/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_82081.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Basaksehir’s manager Okan Buruk, right, argues with a referee during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir at the Parc des Princes stadium in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/a5veku/picture18739501/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_82081.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/qh21gi/picture18740197/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_70252.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Players of Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir leave the pitch, after an argument between the Turkish players and the fourth referee during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir at the Parc des Princes stadium in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/qh21gi/picture18740197/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_70252.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/ri06ts/picture18740203/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_45846.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Fan of PSG, DJ Snake, looks at an empty Parc des Princes stadium during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir, in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. PSG and Basaksehir teams walk off field in protest of alleged racist slur by 4th official during Champions League game (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/ri06ts/picture18740203/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_45846.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/b8zago/picture18740206/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_58208.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Players of Paris Saint Germain, and Istanbul Basaksehir leave the pitch, during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir at the Parc des Princes stadium in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. Basaksehir’s assistant coach Pierre Webo was shown a straight red card in the 16th minute before the players refused to continue the match amid allegations of racism by one of the match officials. (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/b8zago/picture18740206/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_58208.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/xycczw/picture18740287/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_07153.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Players of Paris Saint Germain leave the pitch, after an argument between the Istanbul Basaksehir players and the fourth referee during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir at the Parc des Princes stadium in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/xycczw/picture18740287/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_07153.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/a7a7n7/picture18740293/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_95161.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Players of Paris Saint Germain leave the pitch, after an argument between the Istanbul Basaksehir players and the fourth referee during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir at the Parc des Princes stadium in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/a7a7n7/picture18740293/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_95161.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/5hdtpu/picture18740299/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/APTOPIX_France_Soccer_Champions_League_34429.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Basaksehir’s manager Okan Buruk, right, reacts next to Romanian 4th referee Sebastian Coltescu during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir at the Parc des Princes stadium in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/5hdtpu/picture18740299/alternates/FREE_320/APTOPIX_France_Soccer_Champions_League_34429.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/3j0pzw/picture18740302/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_46757.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>Paramedics leave the Parc des Princes stadium during the Champions League group H soccer match between Paris Saint Germain and Istanbul Basaksehir, in Paris, Tuesday Dec. 8 , 2020. PSG and Basaksehir teams walk off field in protest of alleged racist slur by 4th official during Champions League game (AP Photo/Francois Mori)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Francois Mori</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/3j0pzw/picture18740302/alternates/FREE_320/France_Soccer_Champions_League_46757.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <category>PSG</category>
      <category>Basaksehir</category>
      <category>Interrupted</category>
      <description>The Champions League game between Paris Saint-Germain and Basaksehir has been interrupted after players walked off the field on Tuesday after alleging a fourth official used a racial slur against an assistant coach.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Champions League game between Paris Saint-Germain and Basaksehir was interrupted when players walked off the field on Tuesday after alleging fourth official Sebastian Coltescu of Romania used a racial slur against an assistant coach.</p>
<p>Players from the Turkish team were furious after assistant coach Pierre Webo was shown a red card by referee Ovidiu Hategan of Romania at Parc des Princes, saying Coltescu had used a racial term against Webo, who is from Cameroon, before he was sent off.</p>
<p>Basaksehir substitute Demba Ba demanded that the fourth official explain himself, while PSG players Neymar and Kylian Mbappe also demanded an explanation. Basaksehir coach Okan Buruk said “you are racist” to Coltescu.</p>
<p>The scored was 0-0 when the incident took place about 15 minutes into the match. </p>
<p>Webo was enraged and was heard to repeat at least six times “Why you say negro?” as he sought an explanation from Coltescu.</p>
<p>Moments later, Ba came off the bench and stood in front of Coltescu and said: &#34;Why when you mention a black guy, you have to say ‘This black guy?’”</p>
<p>UEFA replaced Coltescu and pledged to investigate.</p>
<p>“Following an alleged incident involving the 4th official, the match was temporarily suspended. After consultation with both teams, it was agreed that the match would restart with a different 4th official,” UEFA said in a statement.</p>
<p>“UEFA will thoroughly investigate the matter and further communication will be made in due course.”</p>
<p>During the interruption, Basaksehir posted a message on Twitter against a UEFA backdrop with the message “NO TO RACISM.”</p>
<p>Seven years ago, Hategan was in charge of a match between CSKA Moscow and Manchester City when City&#39;s black players were racially abused.</p>
<p>City captain Yaya Toure directed referee Hategan toward fans making monkey noises at the English club’s black players.</p>
<p>Michel Platini, UEFA&#39;s president at the time, requested an internal inquiry involving the referee to examine why guidelines were not followed to respond to discrimination incidents during matches.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:lead-type>picture</newsmail:lead-type>
      <newsmail:lead-image>https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/a5veku/picture18739501/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/France_Soccer_Champions_League_82081.jpg</newsmail:lead-image>
      <newsmail:home-section>Sports</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Biden pide acción urgente contra pandemia y presenta equipo</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739498.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/site-services/newsletters/AUDI_349/article18739498.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>JONATHAN LEMIRE y RICARDO ALONSO-ZALDIVAR</dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/mbk05v/picture18739495/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/CORONAVIRUS-BIDEN_43366.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>El presidente electo de Estados Unidos Joe Biden (derecha) y la vicepresidenta electa Kamala Harris (izquierda) escuchan un video en el que habla el fiscal estatal de California Xavier Becerra, nominado por Biden para ser su secretario de Salud (centro), en el teatro Queen en Wilmington, Delaware, el martes 8 de diciembre de 2020. (AP Foto/Susan Walsh)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Susan Walsh</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/mbk05v/picture18739495/alternates/FREE_320/CORONAVIRUS-BIDEN_43366.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <category>AMN</category>
      <category>GEN CORONAVIRUS</category>
      <category>BIDEN</category>
      <description>Biden pide acción urgente contra pandemia mientras presenta su equipo de salud.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>El presidente electo de Estados Unidos, Joe Biden, pidió el martes que se tomen medidas urgentes contra la pandemia de coronavirus al momento de presentar a su equipo de salud, que trabajará por restaurar un sentido de normalidad en la vida diaria del país.</p>
<p>Biden estableció tres prioridades frente a la crisis de salud planteada por el COVID-19 para sus primeros 100 días en el cargo: insistir en que todos los estadounidenses usen mascarillas en sitios públicos, comprometerse a administrar 100 millones de vacunas y la promesa de intentar reabrir la mayoría de las escuelas del país.</p>
<p>“A partir de nuestro dolor colectivo vamos a encontrar un propósito colectivo”, afirmó Biden. “Controlar la pandemia, salvar vidas y sanar como nación”.</p>
<p>A la cabeza de la lista de su equipo de salud está su nominado a secretario de Salud Xavier Becerra, un político latino de orígenes humildes que se forjó un camino para llegar al Congreso y al frente de la fiscalía estatal de California. Otros incluyen a un hombre de negocios reconocido por sus habilidades en el manejo de crisis y un cuarteto de médicos, entre ellos Anthony Fauci, el principal especialista en enfermedades infecciosas del gobierno.</p>
<p>La presentación del equipo y el anuncio de vacunas se vieron eclipsados por la urgencia del momento, con un promedio de más de 200.000 casos nuevos de COVID-19 por día y un promedio de más de 2.200 muertes diarias, mientras Estados Unidos lucha contra la propagación descontrolada de la enfermedad.</p>
<p>Los asesores científicos del gobierno se reunirán el jueves para hacer una recomendación sobre la primera vacuna en camino: una inyección de Pfizer que ya se está administrando en Reino Unido.</p>
<p>Pero tener una vacuna aprobada es una cosa y aplicarla en los brazos de 330 millones de estadounidenses es otra. Biden será juzgado por lo bien que su gobierno lleve a cabo la tarea gigantesca.</p>
<p>Biden advirtió el martes que la revisión preliminar de su equipo de los planes de vacunación del gobierno saliente de Trump ha encontrado deficiencias. Pidió al Congreso que apruebe una iniciativa de ley que permita financiar la aplicación de vacunas a medida que haya más dosis disponibles el próximo año.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:lead-type>picture</newsmail:lead-type>
      <newsmail:lead-image>https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/mbk05v/picture18739495/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/CORONAVIRUS-BIDEN_43366.jpg</newsmail:lead-image>
      <newsmail:home-section>AUDI 349</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>White Sox reunite with Eaton, finalize trade for Lynn</title>
      <link>https://qa1.kansascity.com/sports/article18739483.html</link>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">https://qa1.kansascity.com/sports/article18739483.html</guid>
      <dc:creator>ANDREW SELIGMAN</dc:creator>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 20:45:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <media:content url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/s0r580/picture18737851/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Rangers_White_Sox_Trade_Baseball_06649.jpg" medium="image">
        <media:description>FILE - In this Thursday, Sept. 24, 2020, file photo, Texas Rangers starting pitcher Lance Lynn winds up during the first inning of the team’s baseball game against the Houston Astros in Arlington, Texas. Late Monday, Dec. 7, 2020, a person with direct knowledge of the deal said the Texas Rangers are trading right-hander Lynn to the Chicago White Sox. (AP Photo/Tony Gutierrez, File)</media:description>
        <media:credit>Tony Gutierrez</media:credit>
        <media:thumbnail url="https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/s0r580/picture18737851/alternates/FREE_320/Rangers_White_Sox_Trade_Baseball_06649.jpg"></media:thumbnail>
      </media:content>
      <category>White Sox Moves</category>
      <description>The Chicago White Sox have reunited with outfielder Adam Eaton and finalized a trade with the Texas Rangers for workhorse starter Lance Lynn.</description>
      <content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The Chicago White Sox reunited with outfielder Adam Eaton and finalized a trade with the Texas Rangers for workhorse starter Lance Lynn on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Eaton agreed to a one-year deal that guarantees him $8 million and fills Chicago&#39;s hole in right field, a person familiar with the situation said Tuesday. The person spoke on the condition of anonymity because the move has not been announced. Eaton&#39;s salary for next season is $7 million. The White Sox hold an $8.5 million option for 2022, with a $1 million buyout.</p>
<p>The signing of Eaton comes one day after the White Sox agreed to acquire Lynn from Texas for pitchers Dane Dunning and Avery Weems. That trade was announced on Tuesday.</p>
<p>Eaton played for Chicago from 2014-2016. He was dealt to the Washington Nationals at the 2017 winter meetings for current ace Lucas Giolito, Dunning and pitcher Reynaldo López. That trade happened a day after the White Sox sent former ace Chris Sale to Boston for infielder Yoán Moncada and pitcher Michael Kopech, launching a rebuild that helped vault them to the playoffs last season for the first time since 2008. Chicago finished second in the AL Central at 35-25.</p>
<p>Eaton spent four years with Washington and helped the Nationals win the World Series in 2019. They declined their option on him after he hit .226 in 41 games last season.</p>
<p>Eaton replaces Nomar Mazara, who struggled last season after being acquired from Texas. Eaton figures to play alongside Gold Glove center fielder Luis Robert, with slugger Eloy Jiménez in left and Adam Engel likely the fourth outfielder.</p>
<p>Lynn is reuniting in Chicago with new manager Tony La Russa. Lynn spent his rookie season with the 2011 World Series champion St. Louis Cardinals, who beat the Rangers in seven games. That was La Russa&#39;s last season as a manager before the White Sox hired him this offseason.</p>
<p>The 6-foot-5, 250-pound Lynn was 22-14 in 46 starts the past two seasons for the Rangers, with 335 strikeouts over 292 1/3 innings. The right-hander has an $8 million salary in 2021, the final season of a $30 million, three-year contract he signed with Texas two winters ago.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
      <newsmail:lead-type>picture</newsmail:lead-type>
      <newsmail:lead-image>https://qa1.mcclatchy-wires.com/incoming/s0r580/picture18737851/alternates/LANDSCAPE_480/Rangers_White_Sox_Trade_Baseball_06649.jpg</newsmail:lead-image>
      <newsmail:home-section>Sports</newsmail:home-section>
      <newsmail:design_category>digest</newsmail:design_category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>